Tinasha's Familiar
Lady Tinasha, how are you feeling...
I'll cut your hair for you!
Aren't you scared of a witch like me?
Witches are frightening, of course.
I'm familiar with the records
of the five witches.
I read that they once destroyed
a nation in a single night.
Why, that's simply terrifying!
However, you don't look like you would do that.
I have a very different
impression of witches now.
I see.
What about you, Lady Tinasha?
Are there things you're
scared of or can't handle?
Can't handle?
There were a lot of things in the past,
but it's all been worn away
after living for so long.
As for now...
I don't like being forced into bed.
What do you mean by that?
Like a child being put to bed?
Also, I can't handle Oscar.
I can never tell what he's thinking.
I think he thinks of me like a cat
he took in off the streets.
You seem to get along wonderfully.
What?
Wonderfully?
~ What the Forest Dreams Of ~
And so, Father, this is
the Witch of the Azure Moon.
I plan on taking her as my wife.
Not happening!
I was trying to keep quiet,
but this nonsense again!
I'm only here to lift his curse.
King of Farsas   Kevin    Oscar's Father
Will you be able to break the curse on my son?
I've run into some difficulty in its analysis.
It'll be some time
before I finish deciphering it.
But, well, I'll figure something out in the end.
Please rest assured.
If you fail, you can take full responsibility.
Don't talk like that!
You really need to start acting like
the crown prince you are!
They seem to be on good terms.
In what way?
For one, you could stop
with the unnecessary comments!
They do get along.
There's more?
We're lucky that she sustained a serious
wound after defeating the demonic beast.
That's how we managed to get our hands on this.
You mean the Witch of the Azure Moon?
Valt
Miralys
Yes.
The strongest of the witches,
as far as I'm aware.
Well, well.
What do we have here?
What nation do you mages hail from?
What are you doing here?
I thought I'd have to clean up after
the whelp that used to be here,
but it looks like that girl took care of it.
She's been searching for you for so long.
I'm aware.
I'll be the one to go and find her,
when the time is right.
I'm sure she'll be delighted.
Delighted?
Absolutely.
She's wanted to see me all this time.
In every history, you treat her
with such arrogance.
In every history?
Whatever could you mean?
It doesn't concern you.
I'm nothing more than a bystander.
You say that, but you appear
to have your own designs.
Nothing of importance.
We help bring about events
that should occur.
That is the sole purpose of our kind.
And if I refuse to let you go freely?
Miralys, run!
That girl is special to me.
I won't allow any unnecessary meddling.
Valt!
Wait, Valt!
No!
Northeastern Farsas    Byle Forest
So this is the forest
where it's been happening.
This place is huge.
We shouldn't do this.
Nine villagers have been left dead,
found as dried, shriveled up bodies!
That's why we need to find the
cause as soon as we can.
We really should stop!
Lady Tinasha will be furious if she finds out!
So it works out perfectly.
She never lets me do anything
when she's around.
But she'll find out if anything
touches my defensive barrier,
so I need to dodge any attack
that comes my way.
I'd rather you just get found out...
A pearl?
Your Highness!
There's a pearl growing here!
How gullible can you be?
But it really does look like...
Lazar!
Wh...
What are these?!
Strange plants?
I-Is this what's been killing people?
I see.
They do look like they'd suck
the moisture out of their prey.
Lazar!
Be good and stand back!
Look, Your Highness!
That's a big one.
Oh no! Poison!
Lazar, let's run for it!
Lazar!
Are you all right?!
What are you doing in these woods?
Lazar.
How do you feel?
Your Highness, am I...
You'll be fine.
She gave you an antidote.
Who?
Good morning.
Th-Thank you very much.
Um, who are you?
Me?
My name is Lucrezia,
but few call me by that name.
Everyone calls me the Witch
of the Forbidden Forest.
Lucrezia    Witch of the Forbidden Forest
Is Tinasha the same as ever?
You know her?
Sure I do.
I've known her since she became a witch.
It was obvious, since she's the only one
who could cast that defensive barrier.
What is she up to now?
Still hiding in that tower of hers?
No, she's acting as my protector now.
What?
So you climbed that tower?
It seemed like a real nasty challenge to me.
His Highness practically
climbed that tower alone!
What, really?
That's incredible.
What contract did you form?
Did you ask to reign over the entire world?
Perhaps.
His Highness wants to marry Lady Tinasha!
Lazar, I swear...
I see, I see.
Thank you.
Well, she turned me down,
so she's my protector instead.
I'm sorry.
But I like the idea.
It won't be easy, though.
Not easy, you say?
It'll be difficult.
That prude has been
a spirit sorcerer for so long.
She's not keen to find a man.
What do you mean?
Among mages, spirit sorcerers
are unique in that they must remain pure.
After mingling souls while having sex,
the magical power needed to perform
spirit magic increases dramatically.
I imagine that with her power,
it'd hardly make a difference, though.
It wouldn't hurt her to try marriage once.
I can help you out, if you'd like.
Would you like me to give you an aphrodisiac?
Normal potions won't work on her,
but the ones I make might do the trick.
No, thanks.
Well, in that case...
How about something more
interesting than an aphrodisiac?
Oh, how scary.
Unlike Tinasha, fighting's not my forte.
So, spare me?
We'll see about that.
Y-Your Highness.
She did save us, and we figured out
the cause of those mysterious deaths.
Let's take our leave for today.
Sure.
Feel free to visit anytime.
Did you face any problems while I was out?
N-Nothing I can think of.
Not at all.
I'm glad to hear that.
Did you finish airing out
your magic implements?
Yes, somehow.
I have many that are tricky to handle,
so I couldn't leave it to my familiars.
I'm sorry for leaving the castle.
Think nothing of it.
In fact, you should take breaks more often...
I'm going out for a bit.
Ah, sure.
What? Do I have something on me?
No, not really.
Oscar, are you feeling well?
Perfectly healthy.
What's this now?
Never mind, then.
Good morning.
Oscar, are you getting plenty of sleep?
I am.
I'm not tired at all.
Oscar.
What's wrong?
No, nothing.
I just felt like I almost remembered something.
You're not fully awake.
Please, just get some proper sleep.
I said I'm sleeping fine.
Why are you so concerned about my sleep?
It's nothing.
Just don't let it get in the way of your work.
She's acting strangely.
G-Good morning.
Good morning.
By the way, I wanted to ask you something.
Wh-What is it?
Has Oscar been getting enough sleep lately?
Probably.
He's not staying up particularly late.
Really?
Really.
How about any recent lovers?
Who are you asking about?!
I mean Oscar's.
None at all.
No one, really?
I swear, there's no one.
Oh, is this jealousy?
Save your nonsense for your sleep.
A...
A lover?!
He seems unaware of it, but his life force
has been fluctuating lately.
If he has a lover,
he should just make it public.
Doan    Farsas Mage
I thought no one would be brave enough.
It's hard to imagine, really...
He reeks of lingering perfume.
I guess he doesn't notice it.
I saw him earlier today,
but I didn't notice any scent.
What?
It's really obvious when you stand next to him.
Wait...
Sorry, I need to go.
S-So scary.
Who would cheat on that?
What was that about?
Oscar!
What's the matter, Tinasha?
Don't give me that!
Why didn't you tell me you met Lucrezia?!
I kept quiet because
I didn't think it was a big deal.
Sorry.
If meeting a witch is no big deal,
then life would be
nothing but trivial matters!
That might be the case.
Please do something about
that stunted sense of danger!
I told you that psychological
attacks can still affect you!
Having confidence is one thing,
but I won't be held
responsible if it kills you!
If it kills me?
Luckily, I noticed in time.
This spell disguises itself
as a lover in your dreams
and gradually steals your life force
through sexual intercourse.
If it acts quickly, the victim ends up
dying in about one week.
What?
You should be having erotic dreams every night.
I bet they get erased from
your memories when you wake up.
How did you figure it out?
The scent.
You smell strongly of flowers,
like ladies' perfume.
Which is why I assumed you had a lover.
I don't.
Or wait, do I really smell like that?
I see.
It looks like I'm the only one
who can smell it.
That damn pervert.
So what do we do?
I'll lift the curse tonight.
Your life force has already begun to flicker.
Forcibly breaking the spell from
the outside could cost you your life.
Which means...
We'll forcibly break it from within.
We have to resort to force, huh?
Just be quiet and go to sleep!
Oscar.
Tinasha.
How tasteless.
Oscar?
My hands!
Oscar...
Please stop...
I beg you...
Help me...
Stop it...
Stop it!
Kill her.
Tinasha...
Good work.
You got back all the life force
she stole from you.
Don't...
make me kill you.
That wasn't me.
Even so.
Why not?
As long as you wield that sword,
you might have to kill me in real life someday.
Are you being serious?
Of course.
Wait!
Get some good rest tonight.
Lucrezia!
It's been a while, Tinasha.
Oh, you let your body grow?
What's the big deal?!
That's some sick taste you have!
The real sick part is
the way you broke that curse.
I didn't think you'd make him snap your neck.
It was the fastest way,
and it made me feel better.
It should be obvious
that I made a contract with him.
Why would you do that?
Think of it as a little greeting
after all this time.
You almost killed someone with that greeting.
Well?
What did that contract holder say?
He got angry because I made
him break my neck.
I mean, sure he did.
Must have left a bad taste.
That'd be rich from the owner of Akashia...
He sure was manly, though.
If you're not interested, can I have him?
Go ahead, take him.
No, I take that back.
What, having second thoughts?
No, it'd be bad to introduce
a witch's blood is all.
Oh, he's caught up
in that whole mess, isn't he?
The Witch of Silence, was it?
Breaking that will take some work.
Let's see...
Here.
Take this.
My way of apologizing.
His blood and sperm.
I think those would be
the most affected by the curse.
You took these from him?
You really should do something about
that awful hoarding habit of yours.
Aren't you a little too angry?
You know, that spell wasn't meant
to make a copy of you.
All I did was have it reflect his own desires.
Whose fault is it that we're
fighting in the first place?
Yours, for being so stubborn, right?
Why don't you go back and just apologize?
I think he really cherishes you.
Step inside.
Come here.
Ah...
I'm sorry.
Sorry...
~ A Breath of Life into Image ~